seatmaestro.com 2015-06-19

# Privacy policy

SeatMaestro® is your best source for airline seat information and detailed seat maps for both regular and low-cost flights. We cover 178 airlines worldwide and we update the information on a daily basis. SeatMaestro offers up-to-date airline seat maps, seat reviews and a color-coded system to find the best airplane seats during your next flight. For each aircraft, we provide detailed information on seat pitch (amount of legroom), seat recline, seat width and in-flight amenities. In addition, we offer airline specific information regarding Check-in, Baggage Allowance, Minors and Traveling with Babies and Pets. Seatmaestro.com was exclusively designed for assisting airplane travelers in obtaining as well as sharing information on airplane seat maps and air travel. It is operated by SEATMAESTRO LLC., a privately held company in Miami, FL, USA. More details about SeatMaestro may be found below under "Contacting Us".

We consider that your own privacy is particularly important to us. The Privacy Policy set herein clarifies how we gather and make use of the information you distribute when you use our website. Please our read this Privacy Policy with great care, and if you have any doubts or querries, do not hesitate to contact us. Despite the fact that this Privacy Policy is not an agreement and does not create any legal rights, it does serve as our declaration to secure your private personal information. Please note that our sites contain links to other sites. SeatMaestro is not responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content regarding these other sites. By using SeatMaestro, you agree to the gathering and use of your personal information as set in our Privacy Policy. Occasionaly, we may update the Privacy Policy and we will post a notice of significant changes on the site. You ought to visit this page periodically to examine any such revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

**Information We Collect And How We Collect It**

**Personal Information**

We do not collect any personal information from a site user unless that particular user clearly and expresedly provides it. Under no circumstances do we gather any personal data referring to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, personal beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life. If you are just browsing our site, we do not collect any personal information about you.

We get as well as store any information you willingly provide to use via our site. This includes personal information information, i.e. data which may identify you, including your first name and surname, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses, user name and password. We may also ask you to provide information referring to your air travel arrangements, your preferences when you fly such as which seat best suits your needs, flight class, baggage as well as ticketing options. You have the option of not providing us any such information but all the data that we require from you will be of great value for us as it will help us both understand and meet your needs.

You will have the possibility to give contact information for other people via our site. However, before doing that, you need to have the approval of the others before providing it to us.

We also collect information about your computer whenever you visit out site. This information is collected automatically and refers, but does not limit, to session data, IP address and Web browser software. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as content viewed and pages visited. One of our aims in gathering this automatic information is to assist us in understanding what interests our users the most and how we may enhance their user experience.

**Cookies and Other Web Technologies**

A "cookie" is nothing more but an item of information that our web site sends to your browser, which then is stored on your system. You need to know that cookies do not contain more information than you volunteer to provide, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender any personal or other information from your computer. Therefore, cookies are small data text files that are commonly stored on your computer's hard drive, provided your browser allows it. This piece of data that identifies you as a unique user SeatMaestro uses cookies in order to:   

  * assist us in identifying your browser as a former user so that our site may save and save and remember your preferences. For instance, cookies may be used in order to remember your registration information whenever you register on our site. Therefore, you will not have to into our site each and every time you visit us. We also may record your password in a cookie so than you may be automatically signed in. However, IDs, passwords alongside with any other account-related data included in these cookies are encrypted for security purposes. 

  * assist us in customizing your browsing experience as well as the content and adverts supplied on our site. For instance, a cookie that is automatically set by us, will come into play in order to display information and adverts that suit your tastes and needs. 

  * improve the quality of our service and make the service easier to use for our users

  * assist us in measuring and analysing the efficacy of our website features, contributions, adverts as well as any other supplied information. 

There is a Help section on your browser which informs you that you have the option of not accepting any new cookies. You also have the option of having your browiser notify you whenever you get a new cookie or your may also disable any or most types of cookies. Therefore, you may disable or delete the cookies at any time.Remember, though, that you may not have the possibility of browsing and accessing some of the tools supplied for you on our site if you choose not to permit cookies.

**Display of Advertising**

SeatMaestro is committed to supplying you with relevant content and information. Thus, we may gather information about your travel-related searches, such as whether you are looking for airline flights or hotels, and use this information to serve you with ads on our sites or elsewhere online that match your apparent interests. Thus, if you happen to seek information about a flight to Miami on SeatMaestro, you may see an advert for a Miami travel package on SeatMaestro or on another website you visit. Please, take account of the fact that we do not share your personal information with any independent third parties so they can supply you with their own adverts.

**How We Use Your Information**

SeatMaestro make uses of the information we gather from you in order to: register and manage your account; communicate with you; allow us to your reviews and any other content to the SeatMaestro community;give an answer to your questions and comments; monitor your concerns in the fiels and better our products, services as well as web site; request information from you, including through surveys; implement our Terms and Conditions.

**How You May Control Your Personal Information**

We also aim to provide you with significant, accurate, to the point, exhausitve information. We also need to ensure that your information is both accurate and relevant. Therefore, you may access your profile on our site any time you need and update your contact information. You also have the option of closing your SeatMaestro account any time your wish. We would like to remind you that we may keep certain information associated with your account in our archives. We do this for analytical aim or recordkeeping integrity. You have complete control of the information you submit to SeatMaestro.

**How We Secure Your Information**

We take great care in protecting all and any personally identifiable information we get from our site users. We make use of standard security measures to protect your personal information so that it is not easily accesible to unauthorized parties. If you would like to know what exact measures and techniques we employ, do not hesitate to contact us. 

**Children's Privacy**

SeatMaestro is a general audience site. It is not meant to offer services directed to children. SeatMaestro does not deliberately gather personal identifiable information from minors under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not give your name and address or any other contact details or personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. 

**External Links**

SeatMaestro may contain links to other web sites. Please note that these other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

SeatMaestro may update this Privacy Policy in the future. You will be notified of such changes by a notice displayed on our web site. We will publish any such changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. Despite the fact that the herein Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights or liabilities, it is presented to you as a statement of our commitment to protecting your private information.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding the herein Privacy Policy please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.seatmaestro.com/contact-us.html). We hope that you enjoy your visit to Seatmaestro. Thank you.
